cypress a testing solution for web applications famous for making
cypress 一种针对 Web 应用程序的测试解决方案，以使
test-driven development fun for javascript developers we all know
javascript 开发人员的测试驱动开发变得有趣而闻名我们都知道
testing is the right thing to do but actually doing it in a front-end
测试是正确的事情，但实际上在前端
javascript project can be complicated slow and just not fun for many the
javascript 项目中进行测试可能会很复杂，速度很慢，而且对许多人来说并不有趣
obvious solution is to simply not test anything at all that's not ideal cyprus
显而易见的解决方案是根本不测试任何不理想的东西 塞浦路斯
provides an open source browser-based test runner that can experience your
提供了一个基于浏览器的开源测试运行器，可以
website just like the end user would it might fill out a login form click the
像最终用户一样体验您的网站，它可能会填写登录表单单击
submit button then navigate to the user dashboard all of which happens
提交按钮然后导航到用户仪表板所有这些都
programmatically based on code you define every test is recorded and a
基于您定义的代码以编程方式发生，每个测试都被记录并
snapshot is saved at each step this makes it possible to time travel through
在每个步骤中保存一个快照，这使得可以通过用户体验进行时间旅行，
the user experience to figure out precisely why your code sucks and unlike
以准确找出您的代码糟糕的原因，并且与
traditional testing utilities debugging can be performed directly from the
传统的测试实用程序不同，调试可以是 直接从
browser dev tools not only does it work for end-to-end testing of an entire
浏览器开发工具执行，它不仅适用于整个应用程序的端到端测试，
application but it's also great for integration testing and unit testing of
而且是一个 非常适合集成测试和
isolated components or javascript business logic to get started install it
独立组件或 javascript业务逻辑的单元测试以开始将其安装
into your project then run npx cypress open notice how this pulls up the test
到您的项目中，然后运行 npx cypress open意它如何自动启动测试运行器并在
runner automatically and creates a folder in the root of your project named
项目的根目录中创建一个名为 cypre
cypress that contains all of your testing code fixtures is where you would
s 的文件夹 包含您所有的测试代码夹具是您
define mock data plugins allow you to hook into the testing life cycle support
定义模拟数据的地方插件允许您连接到测试生命周期支持
is for your global configuration then your main testing code lives in the
是针对您的全局配置然后您的主要测试代码存在于
integration file we can create a test suite with describe then before each
集成文件中我们可以使用之前的描述创建一个测试套件 每个
test we can run some setup code like tell cyprus to visit a specific url from
测试我们都可以运行一些设置代码，比如告诉塞浦路斯从那里访问一个特定的 url
there use it to describe a test case where you might verify that the web page
使用它来描述一个测试用例，您可以在其中验证网页是否
contains a certain piece of content the get method will grab an element from the
包含特定内容get 方法将从 dom 中获取一个元素
dom and allow you to run assertions on it like it should have the text to log
并 允许你在它上面运行断言，就像它应该有登录的文本
in it bundles the chai assertion library for behavior-driven development which
一样捆绑了 chai 断言库，用于行为驱动的开发 w
will autocomplete with intellisense from there you may want to find a form input
hich 将从那里使用智能感知自动完成您可能想要找到一个表单输入
and type something into it after the form is filled out submit it to update
并在填写表单后在其中输入一些内容提交它以更新
your database the great thing about cypress is that it will automatically
您的数据库关于cypress 的好处是它会自动
wait for async events which means you don't need to add a bunch of sleepers in
等待异步事件，这意味着您不需要 不需要在
your test code things just work naturally now run your tests to watch
您的测试代码中添加一堆睡眠者 事情自然而然地工作 现在运行您的测试以观察
everything go down visually a snapshot of the dom is taken for every event if
一切都在视觉上下降如果断言失败，则为每个事件拍摄 dom 的快照
an assertion fails you can easily inspect the dom to see what went wrong
您可以轻松检查 dom 以查看什么
on top of that you can open the selector playground to easily grab any element on
最重要的是，您可以打开选择器游乐场以轻松获取页面上的任何元素
the page by default it runs in chrome but you can also run in firefox edge or
，默认情况下它在 chrome 中运行，但您也可以在 Firefox Edge 或
electron for desktop apps this has been cypress in 100 seconds hit the like
Electron 中运行桌面应用程序，这已在 100 秒内被 cypress 点击“赞”
button and subscribe if you want to see more short videos like this and if you
按钮 如果你想看更多这样的短视频，如果你
want to learn more about testing my friend bartow's just launched a free
想了解更多关于测试我的朋友 bartow 刚刚推出了免费
end-to-end testing course thanks for watching and i will see you in the next
的端到端测试课程，请订阅，感谢观看和 我会在下一个见到你
one